Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art buildings and grounds records, 1870-2007 COR0007.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Correspondence [legacy series], 1919-1970; Series 2
  - Correspondence: Wolfsteiner Co., 1925-1933; Series 2 (Box RG7.0-1999.001, Folder 100)
- Correspondence, Series 9
  - Legal Correspondence, 1988; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Legal Correspondence, 1986; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Legal Correspondence, 1987; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Chase Case, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - New Jersey Sales Contract, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Storrs Materials, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Scottie Donnachie- Fire Door Project, 1988; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Huntingt. T. Block Liability Ins. Renewal, 1988; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Huntington T. Block Insurance Automobile Insurance Information, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Huntington T. Block Insurance Policies General Information, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Student Accident Insurance Huntington T. Block, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Umbrella Liability Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Insurance Art, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Automobile Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Boiler & Insurance Policy, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Cleveland String Quart, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Insurance Accident, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Jack Perlmutter Lecture, 1966 March 24; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Huntington Block, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield Bulletins FY88, 1988; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Worker's Compensation Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Certificate of Insurance "Package Policy", undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Employee Benefits Ins., undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Events Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - First Aid Liability, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Student Accident Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Trustee Liability Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Insurance Correspondence, 1987; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Insurance, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Misc. Insurance Files, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Insurance- Strads, undated; Series 9 (Box 7, Folder 46)
- Architect specifications & contractor estimates, 1894-1933; Series 3
  Includes Ernest Flagg's original 1894-95 specifications for the new building in electricity, heating, iron works, masonry, and plumbing and contractor construction estimates for such work. Also included are some specifications for later years concerning roof repair, electric light modification, and reflector developments.
  - Iron Work: Specifications - Flagg, Circa 1894-1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.001, Folder 106)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Specifications - Flagg, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 1)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, H.D. Bayne and Co., Undated; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 2)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Brooklyn Electric Equipment Co., 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 3)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Charles L. Eidlitz, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 4)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, General Electric, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 5)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Royce T. Marean, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 6)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, McKay-Howard Eng. Co., Undated; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 7)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Norcross Bros., 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 8)
  - Electric Light and Power Plant: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 9)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Specifications - Flagg, 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 10)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Baker, Smith and Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 11)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, E. Norman Beaton, Undated; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 12)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Crook, Horner, and Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 13)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Johnson and Morris Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 14)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Norcross Bros., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 15)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Onderdonk Heating and Ventilating Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 16)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, H.B. Smith and Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 17)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Wells and Newton Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 18)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Wm. E. Wood and Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 19)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Zellers and Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 20)
  - Heating and Ventilating: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Alva Hubbard and Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 21)
  - Maintenance and Repairs - Miscellaneous, 1950-1957; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 22)
  - Iron Work: Contractor Proposal - Campbell and Zell Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 23)
  - Iron Work: Contractor Diagrams of Work, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 24)
  - Iron Work: Contractor Diagrams of Work, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 25)
  - Mason and Carpenter Work: Specifications - Flagg, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 26)
  - Plumbing: Specifications - Flagg, 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 27)
  - Plumbing: Specifications - Flagg, 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 28)
  - Plumbing: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Norcross Bros., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 29)
  - Plumbing: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Wm. H. Quick, 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 30)
  - Plumbing: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Wm. Reynolds, 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 31)
  - Plumbing: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, S.S. Shedd and Bro., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 32)
  - Plumbing: Contractor Proposals and Estimates - Building and Grounds, Wells and Newton Co., 1895; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 33)
  - Work To Be Done: Specification (General) - Flagg, 1894; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 34)
  - Specifications: North Wing Roof Repair (Donn and Deming), 1921; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 35)
  - Specifications for Lighting Fixtures (Frink Co.), 1933; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 36)
  - Specifications for Reflector Developments (Frink Co.), 1933; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 37)
  - Specifications for Reflector Developments (Frink Co.), 1933; Series 3 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 38)
- Maintenance and repair, Bulk, 1960-1978 Bulk, 1960-1978 1924-1978; 1960-1978; Series 4
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  Features budget materials, conference notes, contracts and contract bids, correspondence, memoranda, reports, and studies regarding general maintenance & repair to the gallery building. Pertinent materials include the contracts with the James Baird Company, the Johnson Company, and the Wolfsteiner Company; switchboard modifications by Pepco in the 1930s; electrical renovations done by Frank Sullivan Association in the 1960s; and the staff's renovation & repair requests survey from the later 1960s. The bulk of the records date from the early & mid 1960s and, then again, from the late 1970s. People who figure prominently include Frederick Bradley, Eleanor (Mrs. Leon) Green, Frances harper, Richard Madigan, William O. Snead, and David Stainbeck.
  Separated Materials
  All architectural records have been removed from the files and placed with that series.
  - Air Conditioning (Conventional Units) For Curatorial Dept., 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 39)
  - Amer. Assoc. of Museums Accreditation Questionnaire, 1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 40)
  - Amer. District Telegraph Co., 1951-1963; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 41)
  - Auditorium Equipment, 1959-1966; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 42)
  - Auditorium Equipment, 1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 43)
  - Auditorium Equipment, 1968; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 44)
  - Boiler Room Conversion (Sub-Basement), 1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 45)
  - Budget, 1978-1979; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 46)
  - Building Fund, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 47)
  - Chemical and Steam Cleaning of Gallery Exterior, 1966-1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 48)
  - Chimney Repair, 1975; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 49)
  - Column Repairs-Atrium, Undated; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 50)
  - Column Repairs-Auditorium, Undated; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 51)
  - Condensate Pump, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 52)
  - Contracts - Baird Co., Clark Wing, 1925; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 53)
  - Contracts - Baird Co., Clark Wing, 1926; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 54)
  - Contracts - Baird Co., Clark Wing, 1927; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 55)
  - Contracts - Johnson Service Co., 1926-1927; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 56)
  - Contracts - Wolfsteiner Co., Draft, 1924; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 57)
  - Contracts - Wolfsteiner Co., 1924; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 58)
  - Contract Bios, Miscellaneous, 1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 59)
  - Dupont Center Heating, 1976; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 60)
  - Electrical Renovation, 1961-1963; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 61)
  - Electrical Renovation, 1964 January-June; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 62)
  - Electrical Renovation, 1964 July-December; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 63)
  - Electrical Renovation, 1965; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 64)
  - Electrical Renovation, 1966-1968; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 65)
  - Electrical Renovation, 1971-1972; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 66)
  - Emergency Maintenance Procedures, Undated; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 67)
  - Energy Conservation - Miscellaneous, 1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 68)
  - Fire Protection Systems, 1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 69)
  - Floor Sanding and Waxing, 1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 70)
  - Gardening and Landscaping, 1951-1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 71)
  - Glass Floor Repair and Replacement, 1967-1976; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 72)
  - Hand Rail Installation (Front Steps), 1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 73)
  - Incinerator, 1960-1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 74)
  - Lighting - Interior, 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 75)
  - Ladies' Room Renovation, 1966-1968; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 76)
  - Lighting - Exterior, 1971; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 77)
  - Kresge Foundation Fund (See Also Roof Repair), 1977-1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 78)
  - National Endowment For the Arts, 1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 79)
  - Oil Burner Replacement, 1975; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 80)
  - Priority List of Repairs, 1975-1976; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 81)
  - Solar Energy Research, 1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 82)
  - Switchboard Renovations - Pepco, 1935; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 83)
  - Staff Members Renovation Requests - Administrative Office, Circa 1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 84)
  - Staff Members Renovation Requests - Curatorial Office, Circa 1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 85)
  - Staff Members Renovation Requests - Extension Services Dept., Circa 1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 86)
  - Staff Members Renovation Requests - Finance, Security, and School Offices, Circa 1967; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 87)
  - Steam Station, 1957-1965; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 88)
  - Storage Rack Installation, 1972; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 89)
  - Telephones and Switchboard, 1960-1964; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 90)
  - Telephones and Switchboard, 1967-1968; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 91)
  - Toilets (Pay), 1965; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 92)
  - Ultra - Violet Film/Glare Reduction, 1975-1978; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 93)
  - Ventilation, 1941; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 94)
  - Well - Head Installation, 1962-1963; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 95)
  - Windows Guards (Iron), 1977; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 96)
  - Miscellaneous, 1941-1949; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 97)
  - Miscellaneous, 1960-1963; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 98)
  - Miscellaneous, 1964; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 99)
  - Miscellaneous, 1965-1966; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 100)
  - Miscellaneous, 1967-1972; Series 4 (Box RG7.0-1999.002, Folder 101)
- Special projects [legacy series], 1957-1982; Series 5
  Arrangement
  Materials are arranged alphabetically by project title of subject.
  Includes conference notes, contracts & contract bids, correspondence, grant proposals, guarantees of construction work, memoranda, reports, and surveys of various special plans and proposals regarding major renovation and construction needs. The series contains both those proposals which were realized and those only realized on paper. Important projects covered include the installation of air-conditioning, art school renovation & extension plans, auditorium & basement renovations, the Faulkner Co. architectural survey of the Gallery, Edith Halpert Bequest plans, parking lot renovations & agreements with Corcoran property abutters (United Unions), the major roof repairs of 1977-78, and proposals for a new Corcoran wing (1981-82). It should be noted that many of these subject files are closely related. Where this occurs, "See also" references have been provided in the container listing.
  Persons featured in the files include Frederick Bradley; Henri Dorra; Faulkner, Kingsbury & Stenhouse (later Faulkner, Fryer & Vanderpool); Frances Harper; Richard Madigan; Mrs. Andrew Parker; Roy Slade; William O. Snead; David Stainbeck; Gudmund Vigtel; and Hermann W. Williams.
  - Air Conditioning, 1957; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 1)
  - Air Conditioning, 1960-1963; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 2)
  - Air Conditioning, 1964-1965; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 3)
  - Air Conditioning, 1966; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 4)
  - Air Conditioning, 1967-1968; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 5)
  - Air Conditioning, 1969; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 6)
  - Air Conditioning, 1973; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 7)
  - Air Conditioning Feasibility Study - Shefferman and Bigelson Co., 1973-1974; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 8)
  - Air Conditioning Feasibility Study - Shefferman and Bigelson Co., 1975; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 9)
  - Air Conditioning Feasibility Study - Shefferman and Bigelson Co., 1976; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 10)
  - Air Conditioning - Experimental Installation, 1977; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 11)
  - Art School Extension, 1959-1960; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 12)
  - Art School Extension, 1961; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 13)
  - Art School Extension, 1961; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 14)
  - Art School Extension, 1961; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 15)
  - Art School-Fire Exits, 1959-1961; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 16)
  - Art School - GSA Land - Possible Expansion, Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 17)
  - Art School - Kiln Installation, 1962; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 18)
  - Atrium and Gallery 30 Renovation, 1963 January-May; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 19)
  - Atrium and Gallery 30 Renovation, 1963 June-November; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 20)
  - Atrium and Gallery 30 Renovation, 1964; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 21)
  - Attic Ventilation, See Also Air Conditioning - Experimental, 1976-1978; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 22)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovation, See Also Art School Extension, 1960; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 23)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovation, 1961 January-March; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 24)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovation, 1961 April-May; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 25)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovations, 1961 June-July; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 26)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovations, 1961 August 1-14; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 27)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovations, 1961 August 15-31; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 28)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovations, 1961 September-October; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 29)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovations, 1961 November-December; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 30)
  - Auditorium and Basement Renovations, 1962; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 31)
  - Cafeteria Proposal, 1977; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 32)
  - Climate Control - Climatological Data, 1976-1978; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 33)
  - Climate Control - Grant For Feasibility Study, 1973-1975; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 34)
  - Climate Control - Grant For Renovation, 1976; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 35)
  - Climate Control - Storage Area (Sub-Basement), Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 36)
  - Climate Control - Survey of Other Museums, 1977; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 37)
  - Coleman Report on Building, 1959; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 38)
  - Combustioneer vs. Corcoran - Lawsuit - D.C. Superior Court, 1983; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 39)
  - Conservation and the Gallery Environment, 1976; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 40)
  - Entrance Renovation, 1958-1960; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 41)
  - Entrance Renovation - Museum Shop, 1969; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 42)
  - Entrance Renovation - Museum Shop, 1969; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 43)
  - Faulkner Co. Architects, 1959; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 44)
  - Faulkner Co. Architects, 1960; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 45)
  - Faulkner Co. Architects, 1961-1967; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 46)
  - Faulkner Co. Architects, 1968-1971; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 47)
  - Faulkner Co. - Architectural Survey, 1966; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 48)
  - Faulkner Co. - Architectural Survey, 1966; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 49)
  - Faulkner Co. - Architectural Survey, 1967; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 50)
  - Faulkner Co. - Architectural Survey, 1967; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 51)
  - Faulkner Co. - Architectural Survey, 1967; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 52)
  - "Future Development of Gallery" Report, Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 53)
  - Halpert Bequest, 1961; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 54)
  - Halpert Bequest, 1962; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 55)
  - Halpert Bequest, 1963-1964; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 56)
  - Halpert Bequest, 1965-1966, Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 57)
  - Handicapped - Section 504 Compliance, Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 58)
  - Kitchen Renovations, 1957; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 59)
  - Library Proposal, Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 60)
  - Pennsylvania Ave. Project, 1966-1967; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 61)
  - Roof Repairs - Agreement With Warren-Ehret-Linck Co., 1977 June-July; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 62)
  - Roof Repairs - Contractor Bids, 1977; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 63)
  - Roof Repairs - Guarantee From Warren-Ehret-Linck Co., 1977-1978; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 64)
  - Roof Repairs - Proposal For Work WIth Warren-Ehret-Linck Co., 1977; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 65)
  - Roof Repairs - Misc. Drawings, Notes, Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 66)
  - Wing Addition to Gallery - Keyes Condon Florance Co., 1982-1983; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 67)
  - Wing Addition to Gallery - Arthur Cotton Moore Assoc., Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 68)
  - Wing Addition to Gallery - Arthur Cotton Moore Assoc., Undated; Series 5 (Box RG7.0-1999.003, Folder 69)
- Special projects, Series 10
  - Misc. P.O.'s, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Bldg. Misc., undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Architects Agreement (The American Inst. of Architects), undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Studley Agreement, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Arena & Co. Corresp. II, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Building & Grounds Comm., 1988; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Asbestos - Removal Phase, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Bldg. Grounds Comm Member, 1987 September; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - NYAve/ Construction Budget, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - NYAve Bldg/ Construction Budget 1B, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Bldg./Business Magazine, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - New York Avenue Contractor's Proposal, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Carnegie Endownment Lease, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - DEUPI- Space Planners, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Energy Conservation Proposal, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - New York Ave. Elevator Report, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Building History- Current Building, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - NY Ave/Faculty Concerns, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Feasibilty Report-Hartman-Cox, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - New York Ave. Financial Project Ions, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Geo. Hyman Const. Co. Contact, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Hyman Contracts, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - George Hyman Construction Co. Correspondence & Memorandums, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Hyman Pre-Construction, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Ed Geisinger Expenses, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - HC Design Development Report, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - HC Schematics, undated; Series 10 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Office Building Slides, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Newspapers, circa 1989; Series 10 (Box 24, Folder 2)